

Daniel Dimitrov

Date of birth: 11/08/2000

Nationality: Bulgarian

Gender: Male

CONTACT

8000 Burgas, Bulgaria (Home)

ddimitrov1108@gmail.com

(+359) 887575828

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/ daniel-dimitrov-94593a180/

https://github.com/ ddimitrov1108 (GitHub)

ABOUT ME

I am ambitious and motivated. I can work alone or in a team. I accept criticism and advice from more experienced colleagues in the environment in which I will be placed. I am ready for opportunities and challenges in an environment where innovation, education, and work are valued and encouraged.

WORK EXPERIENCE

08/04/2022 - 01/09/2022 - Burgas, Bulgaria

X-Ray Operator
Fraport Bulgaria

06/2021 - 09/2021 - Burgas, Bulgaria

X-Ray Operator
Fraport Bulgaria

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

09/2019 - CURRENT - Varna, Bulgaria

Computer Science and Technologies

Technical University of Varna

Address Varna, Bulgaria

09/2014 - 06/2019 - Burgas, Bulgaria

System Programming

Professional school of Chemical Technologies "Akad. N. D. Zelinsky"

Address Burgas, Bulgaria

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Bulgarian

OTHER LANGUAGE(S):

English

Listening Reading Spoken Spoken Writing
B2 B2 production interaction B2
B2 B2 B2

DIGITAL SKILLS

My Digital Skills

Good knowledge in C/C++ and OOP / React.js/Redux / CSS, SASS/SCSS / Javascript (ES6) / MongoDB, MySQL / Express.js / Node.js

DRIVING LICENCE

Driving Licence: B